{
    "subject": "resource/Alberto_Giacometti",
    "predicate": "ontology/movement",
    "object": "resource/Surrealism",
    "human_readable": "Alberto Giacometti was associated with the movement Surrealism.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9455877542495728,
            "question": "How did Surrealism influence Alberto Giacometti's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.905068039894104,
            "question": "What art movement was Alberto Giacometti associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8497610092163086,
            "question": "Alberto Giacometti's work often explored themes related to which movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8038184642791748,
            "question": "Can you name an artistic movement that Alberto Giacometti was involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5840288996696472,
            "question": "To which artistic style did Alberto Giacometti belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5610836148262024,
            "question": "Alberto Giacometti is considered a key figure in which art movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4884863495826721,
            "question": "Which artistic trend influenced Alberto Giacometti's sculptures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4873245656490326,
            "question": "What artistic movement characterized Alberto Giacometti's sculptures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3458345830440521,
            "question": "What kind of art is Alberto Giacometti known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3137892782688141,
            "question": "What was the dominant style in art during Alberto Giacometti's career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alberto Giacometti was associated with the movement Surrealism.",
            "html": "dbpedia_480_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of art is Alberto Giacometti known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_480_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What artistic movement characterized Alberto Giacometti's sculptures?",
            "html": "dbpedia_480_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which artistic trend influenced Alberto Giacometti's sculptures?",
            "html": "dbpedia_480_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_480_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_480_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_480_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_480_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_480_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_480_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_480_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_480_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_480_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_480_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that Giacometti's work in the 1930s is among the most important contributions to sculpture in the Surrealist movement and that he was initially associated with the Surrealist movement, which emphasizes the exploration of the subconscious and the irrational."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references indicating that Alberto Giacometti was associated with the Surrealist movement, both directly and through his works and influences. Therefore, the statement \"Alberto Giacometti was associated with the movement Surrealism\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}